Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride
away, we're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun,
while our dreams are never-ending.
So let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Rebecca!
Go to hell!
You're nothing but garbage!
I hope you die, Rebecca!
Yeah, and I hope it's painful!
You're the same of Dressrosa!
They should set you on fire in
honor of your pyro-granddad!
Whatever the old king did back then,
even if she is his granddaughter,
it had nothing to do with Rebecca!
Yeah, couldn't agree more!
The crowd thinks you're even worse than
that scumbag Bartolomeo from Block B.
And that's pretty damn awful.
Sucks to be you.
That's quite enough.
What's this?
Someone's entering the ring.
You're the rudest crowd I've ever seen.
I'm appalled.
It's downright shameful.
It's none other than the Captain
of the Beautiful Pirates!
Cavendish, darling!
He's just so beautiful!
Whoa! Did she die?
If these ladies had been his opponents,
he would have wanted a heartbeat!
He still has that look that
made him famous three years ago!
They never stood a chance!
I don't understand what she
did to inspire such hatred.
This young lady is courageous
enough to fight to the death.
It's easy for you to scorn her.
You're safe up in your seats if
you truly wish to see her dead!
By all means, I invite.
I want you to come down and fight her!
Your voices are like the buzzing
of insects, you heartless cowards.
I won't abide by your cruelty, even
within this arena of bloodshed.
Don't act as though life
and death are a mere game.
Thank you, Faroole.
He just brought the
horse for his entrance?
Wow, Cabbage.
That was actually real nice.
I still don't like you, though. You suck.
Oh, Cabbage!
I'm not even mad about Rebecca anymore!
I just want to see this guy win!
Woo!
Gather the dish! Yeah! Wow! What a charm!
He's got real charisma!
He just swooped in out of nowhere and
turned all those frowns upside down!
Look, I get it, buddy.
I can see why that would bother you.
You tried to prove a point, and
they're just screaming over you.
But hey, what can you do?
Don't let it get you down.
Everybody loves me!
This is great!
That's how you feel?
It's been too long! Excuse me.
Thank you for defending my honor.
That was kind.
Oh, that's all right.
Their reaction did aggravate me.
But you had it much worse.
In any case, though, we're opponents now.
True.
Now that I think about it, there must be
at least a few news reporters in the crowd.
Oh, that means I could
be in the newspaper.
I can hear their praise now.
They'd say, hey, superstar.
And I'd say, who knew?
Just kidding.
Now, all the competitors
are here, so let's battle!
One abstention leaves us with a hundred
and thirty-seven fighters in block D.
This is the ultimate battle royale.
Warriors, get ready and fight!
I'm done.
I love you, Cavendish!
I'll put their heads, Zuleymon,
or Lumpus will finish them off!
You're dead late, Rebecca!
I won't lose, soldier.
You'll see it.
Yellow Cup Squad and Pink Bee
Squad arriving from Greenbelt, sir!
Well done, Leo.
We're all ready, Commander!
Listen well, my friends.
This battle is a chance for
us to reclaim our freedom,
and to restore the honor
of our dethroned King Rick.
As you know, on that sad day, the flamingo
took away the happy life we all shared.
We will never forgive that.
For an entire year.
We've planned for this day.
Though our foes may be
formidable, we shall prevail.
I better listen to their plan carefully.
That way I'll know just when they bail.
Hey, Zorland, we're about to
take a left turn up ahead.
If you don't remember, left is the
side you don't carry your swords on.
You think I'm too stupid
to know right from left?
Yep.
You're not about to fight just anybody.
It's one of Don Quixote's executives.
Her name is Jola.
Her powers turn people and
objects into weird paintings.
It'll be hard to beat her.
You really know your stuff, don't you?
She works with Doflamingo.
I memorized as many of the family's
names, faces, and abilities as I could.
Especially those three.
The top-ranked executives who wiped
out Dressrose's army ten years ago.
Treble, Diamante, and the big guy, Pika.
Those are three faces I'll never forget.
Wait, ten years ago?
But you're a kid!
No, I'm 27!
How's that possible?
Uh, huh? That's Zoro.
I said laugh!
Sir Zoro!
We meet again!
Come over this way!
Hey!
How about some subtlety, huh?
Who are those people?
They don't look too bright.
Allow me to introduce you
to Dumbland and Dumberland.
Whoa, really?
So you're on the way to save Nami?
That's why she didn't pick up the snail.
I knew I sensed a damsel in distress.
All right, I'm coming with you.
But wait, Sir Sanji.
We have vital information
to give to Sir Luffy.
We mustn't abandon that. There you are.
Oh, Violet, my sweet.
That kind of crap is going
to get you killed, idiot.
Listen, Blackleg.
Your ship's been hijacked
by my colleague, Giola.
And they're making their
way to Greenbit now.
Oh, no, this is life.
Nothing like fabulous tombs
on a sea of art. Oh, yeah.
You know culture when you see it.
Turn this ship around.
Don't tell me we're going to Green Bay.
Imagine the look on Law's face.
Should be a shock when he sees it's not
you that's coming to collect Caesar,
but moi.
I don't get why Brooke is acting so weird.
Why did he turn against us?
There's no way.
A true swordsman would
never betray his friends.
Yo-ho-ho-ho!
I've simply reawakened
my true artistic nature.
Bringing forth new creations
is my only reason for living,
despite the fact that I myself
am very dead, of course.
Sing it!
For these peasants can't
understand us, soul king.
We only want to express ourselves.
They'll never know our passion.
Life is the greatest art.
Dying art.
It's not!
Someone help me!
I'm fine doesn't hurt really.
I moved beyond tears.
Look how I've exquisitely depicted
the tragedy of dress Rosa in about ten
Minutes these rooms will be completely
fused with my latest masterpiece.
Choking to death and
turning into a still life.
It's simply splendid—you must let
me compose a song for your exhibit!
exhibit But, uh, first, could you
change my violin and bow back?
You got it.
Take it away, brother!
Whoa!
You miracle worker, you!
My useless consciousness.
I don't want to die like this.
Like to see something interesting?
You'll notice my violin bow is
actually a sword, Giola. Enough talk.
Play me some music.
I decided to cut you instead.
What's that?
My painting song, Bamboo Flute Slices.
You must forgive me.
I don't know art.
One look and I thought it was clear.
After all, I don't have the eyes for it.
Ahhhh!
Sir Skeleton!
Eight centuries ago.
That's how far back this
little story begins, Law.
800 years ago, 20 kings from 20
countries met at the center of the world.
They formed an alliance and
became a single organization.
Today, we know it as the world government.
The kings who created this
governing body decided to move to
the holy land of Mariejoie and
live there with their families.
There was only one,
the Nefertari family of Alabasta,
that refused to reside in the capital.
The descendants of those 19
creators, still dwelling in the city,
control nearly the entire world and go by
the title of Celestial Dragons. However,
we can't forget this
agreement 800 years ago also
caused 19 kingdoms to
lose their royal families.
You following along?
Out of necessity,
the countries needed to select new kings
to govern and replace the missing rulers.
For instance, in the case
of my native Dressrosa,
the Rick family was selected
to govern over the island.
And the old royalty who
chose to move to the
Holy Land of Marie Joie
all those years ago.
The Don Quixote family.
I was worried about Nami
long before you ever were,
and if she wants anyone to come
save her, it's definitely me,
so you let me handle this then
get going already, Kin'emon,
take this map to the toy house
where your friend is being held.
I am eternally grateful
when you see Luffy again!
And contact the Sunny using this.
We need to check everyone's situation.
I'll stay aboard the ship.
So, any idea how we reach him?
If I knew, do you think we'd be
standing here with our arms folded?
The place has been completely sealed off.
And I don't see anyone to let us in.
We should also avoid suspicion,
since I was nearly arrested earlier.
cool so I'll just cut
down the wall I said be
discreet I'll do it quietly
boy that's not the point
that's the legendary
pirate hunter Roro Noa Zoro
they say he chopped up a
hundred men in whiskey beat
sliced and diced everything
in his patent in his
lobby he's He's the master
of the three-sword style.
He's the Straw Hat's first mate.
Luffy's right-hand man.
Even without Devil Fruit powers,
he's a monster on the battlefield.
And he looks so cool in person.
The tears, it won't stop.
My heart is overflowing.
Come on, Gladius.
Why don't you try and settle down?
I can't, Baby Five.
Or perhaps you're blind
to just how much her
betrayal has completely
derailed our well-laid plans.
The idea was simple,
the woman Violet would capture
Blackleg Sanji, then search his mind.
And extract the enemy's
strategies afterwards?
Would be able to predict their every
move and eliminate them one by one,
but what does she do instead?
Wipes out her own men and runs off with
them.
If there's one thing I
absolutely loathe it's
people who can't stick
to a time or a plan.
No one betrays us.
She was disloyal to the young
master and must pay with her life.
Violet was acting strange
as far back as last night.
Think about it, baby.
With Violet's all-seeing eye,
she should have easily been able to
find the Straw Hat ship yesterday.
You're not supposed to be
riding this steed with me!
I told you to wait back at
the harbor, you naughty girl!
I would, but it's growling with my reins.
You and your friends may want to
rethink your rendezvous point.
so the navy's here too
i count four battleships
total that means there are at least three
thousand marines scattered
across the city as
we speak and you found
all that out in such a
short amount of time
it's one of my abilities
clairvoyance my all-seeing eye has a range
of up to 2500 miles
and allows me to survey
the land from a point of
view of a burden flight
From this very spot, I can see
everything going on in Dressrosa.
Bottom line, you don't need
to worry about my safety.
There isn't a person
alive who can catch me.
Uh, does that mean you're
gonna stay in this country?
No, there's nothing to worry about.
But what I am going to do is...
What's wrong? It's bad.
Seems your sheep emerged out of
nowhere and then was hit by lightning.
Hit by lightning?
Then Nami must be safe.
Okay. Cheese toast. Good.
Did you see?
I went two and I took her
out with one big swing.
A clean blow.
Almost like it was muscle memory for you.
D-Do you think so? Thanks a lot!
Well, we can't throw her over.
Yeah, she'd sink.
I think I'll pass on
the panties this time.
Oh? Panties?
You say you'd like to see them?
Trust me, I wouldn't dream
of such a thing, madam!
Should I hit her harder this time?
No, just leave her alone.
We have to go meet up with Traffy.
Right.
He wants us to take
Caesar, but I wonder why.
Look!
Take the ship!
And head for Greenbit now!
I want to leave Caesar with you!
This whole situation is so bizarre.
But Doflamingo did resign from the Seven
Warlords and at our request, I might add.
So I suppose we must return Caesar.
Oh, don't be a fool.
You haven't got a clue, have you?
Huh?
You think the young master
would actually negotiate
with the likes of you?
Just because he said he left the
Seven Warlords doesn't mean he did.
Huh?
That's it.
Tell us what you mean, now.
Did he or didn't he? Ouch!
You brat!
I'll kill you!
No, me!
No, the young master didn't
quit the seven warlords. Sorry,
you've fallen right into our trap and given
Violet the chance to discover your plan.
By now, I'm sure all your
friends have been captured. What?
No way!
So you're a Celestial Dragon?
I don't believe it!
That's me.
Well, that was me, at least.
But not anymore: a man's destiny
has nothing to do with bloodline.
Not many people can say.
They've lived a life as checkered
as I have, that's for sure.
Sorry, law,
believe me—I'd love
nothing more than to knock
back a few drinks and
tell you my life story,
but I don't have time for all that.
The Straw Hats are in dress,
Rosa and I need to address that.
Plenty of others have made the mistake
of underestimating the Straw Hats,
and I don't want to end up like them. So
what
you're done,
not at all—it's just that
I heard a thunderclap
coming from the direction of the sea.
What does the sky look like?
Thunderclap!
I may be blind, but I've always
had a keen sense of the weather,
or at least I thought I did.
Maybe I'm just getting old.
Nami controls the weather, doesn't she?
This ship must be here—hurry up!
You have my heart, don't you?
We'll hand it over.
What is taking you so long?
Give it back at once.
No point—think about
it.
I never said it was Caesar's heart—did I?
What you've been keeping that a secret
all this time—how is that possible?
My heart is missing from my body.
Guess I'm fine.
A marine, really
then—where's my heart?
That's one of my men.
What is the meaning of this?
men what is the meaning of this
Vroom!
Gravity, nice trick.
Keep it up, or else I might get away.
Shambles!
Joker!
Help me!
You've got a lot of energy, Law.
Poor fool.
He should give up.
It's useless.
Let go of me!
And tell me what you did
with my heart, you brute!
You know there's nowhere to run, right?
Wherever you go, I'll catch you.
You see Traffy?
Nah, the fog is way too thick.
Just looks like some weird forest.
Don't get me wrong,
I don't want to believe anything
that old hag told us, but still...
What if, when we go to pick up Caesar,
Law's plan has already backfired?
Well, it's simple.
We're going to die.
No!
Oh, no!
Ow!
What happened?
That hurt. Someone there?
Something's coming this way!
Fighting fish!
An entire school of affairs!
You steered the ship
too close to the island.
What's a fighting fish?
They're monsters, deadly
enough to sink a warship.
That's it.
Keep chasing me.
If he turns his attention to the ship,
And it's all over for us.
First, I need to draw Doflamingo to the
bridge while the others grab Caesar.
Then, I'll just keep him
distracted for a few more minutes.
That way, I can buy enough
time for the ship to leave.
Looks like he's about to cross the bridge.
What for?
That's Dressrosa.
I'll have the advantage over there.
Oh, no.
Idiots, quiet!
Now I get it.
Doflamingo, wait!
This doesn't involve them!
Doflamingo!
I hope you're watching law
because I'm about to eviscerate
your pathetic little We're companions
right before your eyes. No, stop!
Help us! Trapping!
Hey!
You made my crewmates cry!
You're going down!
So easy!
This should be fun. Let's go.